Preliminary Inventory to the George Davis Herron Papers, 1916-1927
Hoover Institution Archives
- BOUND VOLUMES (on shelf)
  - Index to Supplementary Volume.
    - Supplementary: Germany
      - Herron to H.M. Hyndman, Esq., 1919 August 29 (Item I)
      - Herron to Mr. Norman Thomas, 1920 March 25 (Item II)
      - Article by Herron "The American War Motive," 1921 June 25 (Item III)
      - Interview with Herron, published in "L'EPOCA," 1918 September 20 (Item IV)
      - Answers to above questions (Item IV A)
- ORIGINAL DOCUMENTS
  (in manuscript boxes)
  - Volume I. Germany-1 (Box 1.)
  - Volume II. Germany-2
  - Volume III. Austria-1 (Box 2.)
  - Volume IV. Austria-2
  - Volume V. Hungary - Czechoslovakia
  - Volume VI. Italy. Italy and Serbia. Italy and Albania (Box 3.)
  - Volume VII. Bulgaria
  - Volume VIII. Macedonia
  - Volume IX. Roumania. Roumania - The Land. The Near East (Box 4.)
  - Volume X. Russia
  - Volume XI. Switzerland
  - Volume XII. Between President Wilson and Hoover (Box 5.)
  - Volume XIII. The Peace
  - Volume XIV. Supplementary (1-2)
- CERTIFIED CARBON COPIES OF ORIGINAL DOCUMENTS
  - Volume I. Germany-1 (Box 6.)
  - Volume II. Germany-2
  - Volume III. Austria-1
  - Volume IV. Austria-2
  - Volume V. Hungary - Czechoslovakia (Box 7.)
  - Volume VII. Bulgaria
  - Volume VIII. Macedonia
  - Volume IX. Roumania. Roumania - The Banat
  - Volume X. Russia (Box 8.)
  - Volume XI. Switzerland
  - Volume XII. Between President Wilson and Hoover
  - Volume XIII. The Peace (Box 9.)
  - Volume XIV. Supplementary (1-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL
  - Personal correspondence, 1915-1916, A-Z, also unidentified. 1919-1923 (unsorted) (Box 10.)
  - Personal correspondence, 1924-1925, A-Z (Box 11.)
  - Personal correspondence with Professor William F. Badé, 1916-1924 (Box 12.)
  - Cooper Union Lectures
  - Grinnell lectures
  - Reports on European economic conditions and appeals from some European countries. Also clippings (Box 13.)
  - Miscellaneous lectures (3 envelopes)
  - Notes for essays (handwritten) (Box 14.)
  - Outlines of old lectures
  - Correspondence with Antonio Sannini, Firenze, 1916-1927
  - Correspondence with F. Henri Humbert, Florence, 1928 ff.
  - Mrs. Frieda Herron: bills and statements. 1 envelope
  - Family and business papers and correspondence (Box 15.)
    - Sympathy letters and cards
    - Same
    - Obituary notices (clippings and letters)
    - Report cards of Herron's children
    - Calling cards
  - Family and business papers and correspondence (Box 16.)
    - Balance sheets of the Banca Commerciale Italiana
    - Receipts from 1927-1930
    - Criticisms of The Defeat in Victory; The Revival of Italy
  - Newspaper clippings (2 folders) (Box 17.)
  - Newspaper clippings (2 folders) (Box 18.)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 19.)
  - Miscellaneous regarding Socialist Party
  - Poems (Box 20.)
  - Unsorted material, consisting mostly of printed matter and scrapbooks. Includes some correspondence and writings (Box 21-30.)